this is the time known as the great pirate era a countless array of pirates go to battle across
the seas in search of the one piece the legendary treasure left behind by gold roger king of the
pirates makini luffy a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit set sail to
become the next king of the pirates as luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles they capture
the unwanted attention of the world government which will use any means necessary to stop them
can't wait to see what kind of adventures up next with a charted course awash in danger and intrigue
the crew will cut a path across the grand line to the new world
separated from the rest of his crew luffy makes his way to navy hq to rescue his brother ace from
execution meanwhile the other straw hat pirates have adventures of their own
the friends whereabouts the huge tomb and the panty dent
far away but not long ago zorro found himself trapped on a certain gloomy island with perona
i can't take this anymore we gotta hurry
where did that sword swinging simpleton run off to this time
oh come on give me a break i can't find the stinking bedroom
it's like i'm stuck in a maze
what am i even doing this is a waste of time
hide his sword it'll be fun i thought use your negative hollow to make him depressed that'll be
hilarious only i had to tell him where his sword was and two days later he still can't find it
wow zorro i guess you sure showed me right now i'm depressed
why are you here are you trying to use your power to mess with my head i live here and you're depressing
enough without my help besides i told you where your sword was climb the stairs directly behind me
follow the hallway and get your stupid sword back okay do you need me to hold your hand little boy
you keep giving out crappy directions to trick me
have you got brain worms or something that's the wrong way
behind me come on what is your sense of hearing messed up too
i shouldn't have taken his sword away i didn't think he'd be so sad without it
this isn't funny at all in fact it's a tragedy
you're the one who did this to me
keep at it buddy you'll be okay
go zorro
that's enough
here just take it why the change of heart
i'm bored of your antics that's all and it's not like you're any threat to me this form is no
different than one of my ghosts you'd have to attack my real body to do any harm
and the chance of you finding it is like zero
and besides you're not cute enough to be one of my servants
you really think i'm doing this out of kindness dingbat if this plan works out i get back to my life on
thriller bark if you're going to be this stupid i'm almost required to take advantage of you
this spooky little vacation has been fun enough but you're my ticket out of here and i'm going to use you
i'm going to use you lucky me huh
why didn't i see that coming i've got to stop freaking out and follow him
he'll just get lost again what is he thinking
i gotta get back to saba ori it's been too long already and we were in pretty bad shape when i
got sent away i just hope everyone made it out all right everyone start running and look after
yourselves we can't win this one we're too weak get moving wait do i
i can't just stay here doing nothing it could be hurt or worse
that castle looks familiar i think
oh i get it it's like the other one why don't they build two
so that's how your head works how did you ever survive for this long
i really have a kind heart don't i i don't have to guide him to the sea but here i am
well he'll be doing me a favor in the end so no biggie you sure this is the right way to go
don't you dare you're gonna get us lost you aren't allowed to complain no more talking just follow
in silence sounds good
so much for you following me you idiot what's that did you forget that i'm leading the way or what
i don't know i guess you're just a bad leader oh it's my fault of course
i'm not even really here and he's wearing me out
what's the deal don't act tired you're not even walking it's you i'm tired of you what did i do
just ignore him piranha don't lose your cool this tree looks kind of familiar we're in a forest
what was that huh maybe that kuma guy sent someone else here too i'd better go check
hey where are you going i'm getting out of here because i just found out that i don't need your
useless hide after all you could walk in circles till you die
i wonder who it is i just hope it's someone a little cuter this time
hey you came back huh
what are you doing here why wouldn't i be here the ocean is this way isn't it
well i mean yeah but it's not like you could figure that out he isn't human
he's a god of trickery sent to torment me or something
it looks like someone did that recently ugh what a letdown it was just a tree falling
guess it's back to my original plan i was really looking forward to dumping him though
oh you know i do cherish these abandoned battlefields delightfully morose
maybe that fallen tree was the work of tortured souls trapped in their place of death
i've got a different theory on that
oh
hey don't go wait
what the heck is this
it looks like a grave the questions who made it whoever they are they've got some skill was carved
straight out of the tree i don't know if this is good creepy or bad creepy
there it is again i knew someone was here
all right
so
guys
Damn it! Strong, too!
Oh! Look out!
What are those things?
This is Lazy Bones Island in the Land of Poverty,
Hungaria. Sent here by Kuma, Brooke was mistaken for Satan by the island's
inhabitants.
How lovely. Another perfect day.
And yet, so lonely. If only I could share the sunrise with my friends.
Yes, I'm sure I can someday, because whatever happens, the sun will always rise. So long
as I stay alive, I have hope we will all meet again.
My goodness, this island certainly is in an unfortunate state though, isn't it? And
such a strange place. I didn't think about it much yesterday. But that house was full
of oddities. Those dolls, and the strange tapestries atorning the wall. Not to mention all the macabre-looking
decorations. It seems they were performing some sort of ritual, but I can't guess the
purpose.
It's rather foreboding, even if they were kind to me.
Oh, good. You're awake. We were just about to bring you an offering of breakfast, as I'm
sure you must be quite famished after your journey to the realm of humans.
My, how considerate of you.
Oh, it's the least we could do.
Such kindness, and from total strangers. You have my gratitude.
Forgive me. I should have introduced myself first. I am the leader of this humble country.
You may call me Peccari.
Well, Peccari, thank you. I shall relish this gift of yours.
Young lady.
Would you be so kind as to show me your panties?
It shall be! Everyone, show him your underwear!
Oh, no, no, no! That's quite all right! Just the young lady will be more than adequate!
Please, there's no need to be bashful. We have plenty to go around.
Really? I've had my fill!
Thank you so much for this generous feast. My stomach's so full, I can skip it.
I can't scarcely move!
That was a joke, you see. I clearly don't have a stomach, after all.
That food was supposed to last us all week!
Shh! Be patient for now.
Uh, Lord Satan, I believe you mentioned that you wanted to ask us a favor.
Yes, I need to set sail right away. Do you have a ship?
But, my lord, has one of us done something to displease you?
Uh, no, no!
Ah! Everyone, quickly! Show him your underwear!
Enough with the under... Whoa!
Is our underwear not good enough anymore?
No, your underwear is perfectly fine. I have been separated from my friends, you see.
I'm afraid I must return to them, whatever the cost.
Return to them?
Yes.
At... At any cost, you say?
Yes. I must go. I'm truly sorry.
Then we're finished.
If our undergarments no longer satisfy you, we have nothing else to give.
Our beloved country will die.
The suffering will only get worse.
We should just take our lives now.
No need to overreact. I'm sure we can come up with something.
Like what?
For starters, could you tell me a bit more about your situation?
Why do you call me Satan, for example?
And what was it you mentioned about the Longarm Tribe last night?
I may be able to help you yet.
Our dear country has long been overrun by the cruel and vicious members of the Longarm Tribe.
Not only do they take our money, our food, our belongings, but they also strike down or enslave our sons and daughters.
As you can see, it's left us devastated.
We scarcely have the clothes on our backs.
Then that food you gave me...
I'm ashamed to say it was all we had.
We felt we should make some sort of offering.
Oh, no.
There was nothing we could do to escape our terrible fate, except pray to every god and goddess we could name and many who were long forgotten.
And when that failed us, we called upon the powers of witches and sorcerers in the hopes that they could curse our enemies to death.
And then, in the end, we turned to the blackest magic of all and called you.
So desperate was our plight, we would summon even the lord of all evil into our midst.
Lord Satan, we can take no more.
Our people are doomed without your aid.
Face the Longarm Tribe and deal them a bloody blow.
We beg of you!
You think I can?
Yes, preferably curse them to death.
Although at this point, just about anything will do.
Please, my lord!
I, uh...
It's the Longarm Tribe!
Oh, no!
Help!
You're in trouble this time!
Do you hear me?
Put her down now!
Help!
I'll reward you again!
Let my daughter go!
We've had enough of this!
We'll give you a taste of hell!
Ah!
Don't let them take me away!
Uh, they're not really kidnapping her, aren't they?
Uh-huh.
Hmm.
Unless you cursed them.
Yes!
Now's the time!
Never mind that!
Should we be chasing them?
Oh, I'm Satan!
Ah!
They're too late!
But, why didn't they do anything?
She's their friend, their family!
Ah!
You can't even fight back?
Did you hear us, Satan?
Did you?
We were cheering extra hard.
You can save us now, Dark Lord.
Give it your best.
I see what got them in this situation now.
They're lazy.
But that young lady is still a victim.
I can't allow her to suffer such a cruel fate.
I will save her.
At the very least, I owe you for the food,
not to mention the panties.
Yeah!
Lord Satan!
You must forgive me, Luffy.
Everyone.
Right now, I'm rather busy being Satan in a sea of underwear.
I'm afraid our reunion will have to wait.
I owe my odd new friends a debt of gratitude.
But I am confident that I shall resolve this quickly.
And I hope you keep safe until then.
It's been almost an hour since we've let Impel down and the winds are strong.
It's odd that we haven't reached Navy headquarters yet.
You don't think you can hurry it up a bit, do you?
Huh?
At this rate, there won't be any carnage left for me by the time we get there.
Calm yourself.
Those Navy bastards better not kill Whitebeard.
Because that's my job.
You still insist on that?
If you want to piss and moan about it, I'd be happy to kill you first.
What's wrong, friend?
I'm coming for you, Ace.
It's not over.
Not yet.
I'm coming for you, Ace.
It's not over.
Not yet.
I'm coming for you, Ace.
It's not over.
Not yet.
What's wrong, friend?
I'm coming for you, Ace.
It's not over.
Not yet.
I'm coming for you, Ace.
It's not over.
Not yet.
Luffy and company continue on the tub current, with Marineford looming on the horizon.
Staring impatiently at his brother's fever card, Luffy is reminded of more innocent times.
Then in nearby waters, Ace is haunted by a recollection of his own.
On the next, One Piece. Retrospective before Marineford. The vow of brotherhood.
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!